WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.MY-SUBS.com -
("THE WHITE LOTUS" THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
(THEME MUSIC CONCLUDES)
(WAVES CRASHING)
(MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(CAMERON SULLIVAN BREATHES DEEPLY)
(INHALES SHARPLY, GROANS)
(GROANS) Oh, shit.
(GRUNTS, BREATHES HEAVILY)
- Okay.
- (LUCIA GROANS)
Okay. Okay, wakey, wakey.
- Come on, come on, let's go.
- (LUCIA GRUMBLES)
- Let's go. We gotta go.
- (MIA MUTTERING IN ITALIAN)
(CELLPHONE BUZZING)
(CELLPHONE BUZZING CONTINUES)
- (ETHAN SPILLER GROANS)
- (MUSIC CONCLUDES)
Hello.
You never sleep this late.
Ah, it was, uh...
Yeah, it was... it wa...
it was a late night. Yeah.
What'd you guys do?
Uh. We just drank all day.
Cameron, um,
Cameron wanted to drink, so, uh...
Yeah, I drank too much.
Well, I've been abducted.
She fully planned to
spend the night here.
She rented this gigantic villa,
and it was a done deal when we got here.
And she didn't even tell me
until we got out of the car.
(SIGHS)
I tried calling you multiple times.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'll miss you.
You sound weird. I guess I'll
see you in a couple of hours.
Yeah, I'll see you when
you get back. Love you.
Bye. (GROANS)
(CALL DISCONNECTS)
(INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
Okay. Here we go. Uh, 15, 16, 17...
Sh... Ah. Eighteen hundred, that's...
that's all I got right now.
- You don't have the money?
- CAMERON: No,
but I'm gonna get the
rest. It's all good.
I'll go to the bank.
We're here until Friday.
I'll leave it in an
envelope at the front desk.
Oh, yeah. Good idea. Do that.
- Yeah. What's your name?
- Lucia.
- Greco.
Lucia Greco. Perfect.
Okay, let's go.
Choo-choo! Here we go. (CHUCKLES) Okay.
Grazie mille. And, um,
thanks for all the fun. Bye.
(DOOR SLAMS)
"Thanks for fun?" (SIGHS)
Luci.
(IN ITALIAN)
VALENTINA: Buongiorno, eh?
MIA AND LUCIA: Buongiorno.
(CHUCKLES MOCKINGLY)
(ISABELLA LAUGHING)
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
- (MUSIC CONCLUDES)
- Ciao, Rocco.
Ciao, Valentina.
- ISABELLA: Ciao.
- VALENTINA: Ciao, Isabella.
- (IN ENGLISH) Happy to take them off you.
- Thank you.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(IN ITALIAN)
No.
Ah.
DOMINIC DI GRASSO: Buongiorno.
VALENTINA AND ISABELLA: Buongiorno.
(IN ENGLISH) Hello. I was
hoping to buy a present
for my wife today. Uh,
she couldn't make it,
- unfortunately.
- ISABELLA: Hmm.
Uh, maybe a nice piece of jewelry,
so I was wondering if there's a store
you'd recommend.
No, I don't know.
But you could, uh, walk along the corso,
and you'll find something.
There's a wonderful
store called Pancrazi.
It's very near, and it's very nice.
Great. Grazie.
- You're welcome.
- Prego.
Grazie.
(IN ITALIAN)
Ah.
(INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING)
Okay. Grazie mille.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
PORTIA: (IN ENGLISH) I'm
just gonna get some fruit...
really quick. I'll be right back.
Okay?
- Okay.
- (MUSIC CONCLUDES)
- Hey!
- PORTIA: Hey.
ALBIE DI GRASSO: How'd you sleep?
- Uh, not good.
- No?
No. We... we really should've hung out.
I'm sorry that I
was... (BREATHES DEEPLY)
I don't know why...
Just... Last night was...
No. It's... it's fine.
Don't... don't be sorry.
Yeah. Uh, we should
definitely hang out today.
Okay. Yeah. That'd be fun.
Yeah, I... I just have to get out
of babysitting, you know?
It's been a lot.
I just have to deal with
that. And then, um...
Yeah, maybe we can, like,
plan something after breakfast.
Okay. Good luck. (CHUCKLES)
- Cool.
- ALBIE: Okay.
- (CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
- ALBIE: See you in a bit. Bye.
PORTIA: So, I know
I'm, like, on the clock,
technically, for today.
Uh, but I was just wondering
if... if it'd be okay with you
if I just hung out with that
guy that I met here for a little?
He's nice and smart. He
went to Stanford and...
and he's not non-binary.
Yeah, I just mess everything up.
I feel like if I won the lottery,
I'd throw away the ticket.
So, I just feel like I...
should give him a chance, you know?
(EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
I don't know what's
going on with Greg...
(PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING)
... but I think it's bullshit.
- (SPEAKING ITALIAN)
- (MUSIC CONCLUDES)
(IN ENGLISH) So chic.
Oh, oh...
Thank you.
You have impeccable style.
The moment I saw you last night,
I said to Matteo, "Finally, a
glamorous woman in Taormina."
Thank you.
QUENTIN: Oh, it's just the color.
All the women here
dress like they're going
to a funeral on the beach.
But you, thank God
you're here. (CHUCKLES)
We're just going to breakfast.
Do you wanna join us?
Oh, no, that's okay, 'cause we just ate.
Do you think we might see
you at the beach club later?
Oh, yeah,
I... I've never been to
the beach club. Is it nice?
Come down, have a cocktail.
We always get the best seats
'cause Marco's an old
friend who looks after us.
Are you English?
- QUENTIN: Ah. I am.
- Oh.
- QUENTIN: Yes, originally.
- (CHUCKLES)
But I live here now in Palermo.
We've got a couple of
friends staying in the hotel,
so we took the boat 'round to meet them.
You have a boat, huh?
- Yes, come down.
- (CHUCKLES)
Come see the boat.
We'll save you two chairs.
- See you later. I hope.
- (CHUCKLES)
Bye-bye.
Those guys are nice.
(PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING)
(LUCIA SIGHING)
(SNIFFLES)
(IN ITALIAN)
- (MUSIC FADES)
- (LUCIA BREATHES DEEPLY)
(MIA SIGHS)
Mia...
(CHUCKLES)
No, no. Ah, Lucia. (SMACKS LIPS)
(LUCIA SIGHS DEEPLY)
Oh!
- Luci.
- BERT DI GRASSO: (IN ENGLISH) Mount Etna.
(IN ITALIAN)
BERT: (IN ENGLISH) We should climb it.
ALBIE: Not sure you're
up for that, Nonno.
(IN ITALIAN)
BERT: (IN ENGLISH) Yeah. I could do it.
(INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING)
That looks inviting. Let's try it.
- Um, I'm gonna just... head back to the room...
- Come on!
Have something with me.
ALBIE: (SIGHS) I just ate.
BERT: Well, perhaps you'll have a drink.
LUCIA: (IN ITALIAN)
- (MUSIC CONTINUES)
- (DOOR CLOSING)
(GROANS)
(SIGHS)
- (SIGHS, BREATHES DEEPLY)
- (MUSIC CONCLUDES)
(IN ENGLISH) Dude.
Jesus Christ.
- This is all your fault.
- (SIGHS)
Come on. We had fun.
(GROANS)
Bro code?
- ETHAN: Bro code?
- (CHUCKLES)
Yeah, baby, bro code.
Sure, yeah, whatever. Bro code.
Thank you.
I love you.
- I just wanna be inside you.
- No, thank you.
- CAMERON: Please.
- No, ma'am.
CAMERON: I wanna do stuff to you.
- No.
- I wanna make you feel good.
(GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING)
(ETHAN EXHALES DEEPLY)
- Oh, fuck!
- CAMERON: You okay?
(GAGS)
(RETCHES)
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
You okay, buddy?
(ETHAN RETCHES)
- (MUSIC CONTINUES)
- (BIRDS CHIRPING)
So, I was really high last night.
Um, and I said a couple things I hope...
(MUSIC FADES)
... stay between us.
Mm. You didn't say anything.
I have trouble keeping
girlfriends sometimes. I mean,
you know how girls are. (CHUCKLES)
They pretend they wanna be your friend,
but really they just wanna
get something out of you
and then talk shit and
stab you in the back.
But I feel like I can trust you.
- Can I?
- (CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
- For sure.
- (CHUCKLES)
Plus, you don't know anybody.
I mean, you don't know any
of the people that I know.
(CHUCKLES)
No. I mean, probably not.
(INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING)
Mia?
Mia.
(IN ITALIAN)
- (MUSIC CONTINUES)
- Um...
(IN ENGLISH) Portia says she's
heading down to the beach club.
I might meet her there.
Oh, your dad and I
can join you for lunch.
Uh, maybe. I was kinda thinking
of just having a day,
you know, for myself.
I don't understand, you don't eat lunch?
I think, let's just
play it by ear, yeah?
- Yeah, all right.
- (CARD READER BEEPS)
- (LUCIA GASPS)
- (SCREAMS)
(YELLS) Uh... So... Sorry.
- (MIA CHUCKLING)
- Sorry, wrong room!
LUCIA: Yes!
- (LAUGHS)
- ("PICCOLO PICCOLO" BY ROBERTINO PLAYING)
I'm so sorry! We... We
thought it was our room!
- Arrivederci.
- We are sorry.
Buona giornata!
(MIA LAUGHING)
(SONG CONTINUES)
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
(IN ENGLISH) That's the
weirdest voice I've ever heard.
- Hey! Hi! So glad you came!
- Hello.
Come back around and up.
Okay.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER AND LAUGHTER)
Bellissima. Sorry, I'm already drunk.
- (TANYA MCQUOID-HUNT CHUCKLES)
- QUENTIN: Hello. (KISSES)
What can I get you to drink?
Wow, yeah. Um, okay.
- All right here. Okay.
- (CHUCKLES)
I'm gonna have some
rosé if you have it.
- Rosé?
- TANYA: Yeah.
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
(RESPONDS IN ITALIAN)
(IN ENGLISH) So, you've met Matteo
and these are our friends
in for the weekend...
- Oh, hi.
- ... Hugo and Didier.
- Hello.
- Hey.
- Bonjour, bonjour, bonjour.
- TANYA: Hi.
- You're French, right?
- DIDIER: Yes! (KISSES)
- Oh, my gosh.
- (DIDIER CHUCKLES)
Didier's family have the most
incredible family estate in Èze,
which you have to see before it crumbles
entirely to the ground.
It is my masterpiece
but it's ruined my life.
- Yes.
- TANYA: Of course, yeah.
Yeah. Take it from me,
I know how that is. I do.
- DIDIER: Yeah.
- Jack! Jack!
This is my naughty nephew, Jack.
All right, all right. Hello, hello.
It's nice to meet you, darling. (KISSES)
- PORTIA: Oh. (CHUCKLES)
- Oh, shit! I know you.
You were by the pool last night.
- I was. Yeah, um. Hi, again.
- JACK: Yeah.
You been in it? It's not heated, is it?
Um, I... I don't know.
I haven't been in it.
Should we get some
panelle, some fritto misto?
Finger food is always a must. Anyway...
- Oh! Thank you.
- Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
- That's it!
- Let's go.
- TANYA: Oh!
- Salute!
ALL: Salute!
("FACILE DA DIRE" BY
SACHA DISTEL PLAYING)
- (SONG CONCLUDES)
- So, you're from America then?
- (DRINK POURING)
- PORTIA: Yes.
- I've never been.
- PORTIA: Really?
- JACK: No, I ain't been to shit.
- Hm.
I'm from Essex, so...
Well, I've been to Essex.
(CHUCKLES)
So, uh, how long have
you been in Sicily?
Two months in Palermo.
- Two months?
- JACK: Mm.
That's... that's amazing.
Yeah, it's all right, if
you don't mind a bunch of...
gays grabbing your
arse and copping a feel.
Do you mind? (CHUCKLES)
No, no, but, like, you
know, these guys get...
pissed. And some of them
are really fucking strong
- as well.
- (PORTIA CHUCKLES)
They have these parties
out in the villa.
Mm-hmm.
And the only women they
invite are just old, rich hags.
I mean, like, you know,
they're nice and that, but...
I didn't come to Sicily to
have tea with old ladies.
Yeah.
I've, um... I was kind of hoping that
Sicily would be more of
an adventure, you know.
But so far, it's just been...
soul-crushing.
- Soul-crushing?
- PORTIA: Mm-hmm.
Fucking hell.
All right. Well then,
if you want an adventure,
stick with me!
'Cause I know how to
have fun in the sandbox.
If you know what I mean.
I... I... (CHUCKLES)
... don't know what you mean by that.
I'll teach you.
(RELAXED MUSIC PLAYING)
Okay. (CHUCKLES)
(CONVERSING IN FRENCH)
(IN ITALIAN)
YOUNG GUEST: Hmm.
(IN ENGLISH) Matteo.
(IN ITALIAN)
Allora... (CONTINUES CHATTING)
(BREATHES DEEPLY) Oh.
(IN ENGLISH) This place is so beautiful.
It is.
I just wanna know the...
What... what is that?
Isola Bella.
There's a story attached to that island.
- Yeah.
- QUENTIN: There's a house on it.
It was owned by a
wealthy Swedish family,
and the old matriarch was
the last one living in it.
(MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
And there were these
powerful local investors,
if you know what I mean,
who wanted the house, wanted the island.
(SEAGULL SQUAWKING)
But the old battle-ax wouldn't budge.
They made her all kinds of offers.
And then one day, her body was found
in a heap at the bottom of the rocks.
(WAVES CRASHING LOUDLY)
They killed her?
Oh, my God!
But now, the house
is open to the public,
so maybe it was worth it.
(LAUGHS)
(CHUCKLES) We should go and see it.
You're just here with
your assistant, right?
No, no, I... I...
I actually came here
with my husband, uh...
but he left.
(EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
He left you alone in Sicily?
Why would he leave you?
- It's a long story and...
- QUENTIN: Well, we have all day.
Tell me everything from the beginning.
Well... (SIGHS)
(INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING)
I was born in San Francisco.
Oh, from the very beginning.
- Okay.
- And, um...
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
- DAPHNE SULLIVAN: Hi.
- ATTENDANT: Here you go, miss.
DAPHNE: Thank you.
Bye.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you, Francesco.
Bye, thank you. (BLOWS KISS)
(CARD READER BEEPS)
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
Hey.
Oh, my God. (EXHALES DEEPLY)
Oh, I'm so glad to be back.
Nice dress.
Daphne bought it for me in Noto.
They didn't clean the room?
Oh, yeah, sorry. The maid did come.
I was just still in bed, so...
How'd it go?
It's what I thought.
It's a front.
The whole thing, the
whole kissy, perfect thing.
- It's a front.
- Yeah.
He cheats on her.
Why do you say that?
HARPER SPILLER: Because
she basically told me.
And I think she does it, too.
- Really?
- HARPER: Yes.
I mean, she was super vague.
But the point is, they
have a twisted relationship,
and we are fine. (CHUCKLES)
Compared to them...
we are fine.
I'm happy to see you.
Yeah?
(CHUCKLES) You got drunk?
The Jet Skiing was fun.
Oh, and she has no women
friends, like, at all.
I'm, like, basically
her best friend now,
and I barely know her.
Isn't that crazy?
Why does she have no female friends?
Because she basically realized
that they were all talking
shit behind her back.
Kinda like you are now?
Okay, so she gave me an edible,
which I know was a mistake.
I know, I know, I know.
I might need to go to the bathroom.
But I started tripping out,
like... (SIGHS) ... crazy.
You know how I get.
- Yeah.
- HARPER: It was a disaster.
I'm, like, going down
the wormhole, like...
(INHALES DEEPLY) ...
so high. Just, like...
- ETHAN: Mm-hmm.
- ... everything that's coming out of her mouth,
I'm just like, "What?"
- I gotta... (CLEARS THROAT)
- HARPER: I'm like, "Wow!"
You know? And, like,
she thinks that, like,
everybody wants to be her,
- everybody wants her life.
- Yeah.
No. (SCOFFS)
(WATER RUNNING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(ETHAN SIGHING)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
Okay. (EXHALES DEEPLY)
I think I can rally. (INHALES DEEPLY)
So, uh, what do you wanna do today?
Do you wanna do something just us?
Do you want me to see
what they wanna do, or... ?
Um, I guess.
ETHAN: All right. Cool. (EXHALES)
Hey! Hi, so, uh, yeah, what do you...
Go to the beach?
(MUSIC INTENSIFIES)
(BAG ZIPPING SHUT)
(WATER BURBLING)
(SEAGULL SQUAWKING)
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
(SIGHS)
MIA: Um...
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(MIA SIGHS)
- Huh?
- (IN ENGLISH) Oh, sorry.
Sorry, hi. Excuse... Excus-ez me, sorry.
Um, I... You can't sit there.
I'm just... I'm saving this seat.
You don't want us to sit here?
Oh, I'm just... I'm
saving it for my friend.
(IN ITALIAN)
(IN ENGLISH) Can we sit
here until your friend comes?
Uh... I just... I think
she's coming any minute now,
- so...
- LUCIA: Oh.
ALBIE: Yeah.
I've seen you around.
(IN ITALIAN)
LUCIA: (IN ENGLISH) Yeah!
I've seen you around.
PORTIA: Cool, taste the rainbow.
Sounds like something
out of Willy Wonka.
So what's Palermo like?
Palermo's fucking wild. (CHUCKLES)
It's mental, man. People just...
They party in the street,
and they fight in the street,
and they fuck in the street.
- It's my kind of town.
- (CHUCKLES)
Is this villa just like...
- Ah, Portia, it's the tits.
- (PORTIA CHUCKLES)
It's so fucking nice.
You gotta come see it.
- I would love to come see it.
- JACK: Would ya?
- Yes. (CHUCKLES)
- JACK: Yeah?
I don't think there's ever been a...
a woman under sixty inside of it.
- So, you would be the first.
- I'm all right with that.
ALBIE: Hey.
Um, hey, I'm... I'm Albie.
All right, geez.
So, I... I saved you a chair over there.
I think I got the last one, so...
- (LIVELY MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
- Oh! Cool.
Yeah. Thank you. Um...
Yeah, I think I just
need to be here with Tanya
just a little longer,
and these guys just ordered
us all this food, so...
ALBIE: Um, yeah, seems like
there's a party going on or something.
I mean, I do wanna hangout,
so I'll come find you and...
- Yeah, I'm...
- PORTIA: Yeah.
- I'm right over there.
- PORTIA: Okay, I just...
- DOMINIC: Albie!
- PORTIA: You know.
- We got a table. Hi, Portia.
- PORTIA: Hey!
Yeah, I'll... I'll find you,
okay? Um... (CLICKS TONGUE)
Well, I'll... Uh, yeah.
I'll see you later.
- PORTIA: See ya.
- Nice to meet you.
JACK: Who's he?
Oh, gosh, he's this guy that I...
I... I met at the hotel, and...
- I think he likes you.
- Mm-hmm.
(INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING)
- BERT: Albie!
- DOMINIC: Hey.
I want you to see what I got.
What do you think?
Like, what?
It's for your mom. Think she'll like it?
It's nice, right? Wasn't cheap.
Oh! It's perfect. She's gonna love it.
DOMINIC: I got some
earrings for Cara, too.
(SCOFFS) You can't just
buy people off, Dad.
It's a gesture, Albie.
Like I said, I'm happy to talk to her.
No. She's not gonna listen to you.
She respects me.
Not in this area, no, she does not.
The only person that
she'd actually listen to
is probably...
But, whatever.
I'm not gonna be your
advocate in this, Dad.
I get it. I understand.
That's fine. That's fair.
I just think,
probably want the family
to stay together, but...
That is... Wow, that is so manipulative.
What?
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
I have to go.
Sorry.
BERT: Uh, no, no, no.
He'll be all right. He'll be all right.
Ciao, how are you dear?
- I think, uh...
- Sì.
BERT: I think we're ready to order.
- DOMINIC: Go first.
- BERT: Tell me something.
What are these numbers...
- Wow.
- ... beside all these dishes?
- DOMINIC: Yeah.
- BERT: Are those the prices?
DOMINIC: Why are you
worried about the price?
It's not like you're paying
for anything, all right.
Nice!
- Menus.
- Four spritzers. Thanks.
ETHAN: We shouldn't even be drinking.
CAMERON: Oh, come on.
Hair of the dog, man.
ETHAN: I just don't
wanna throw up again.
DAPHNE: Wow, you guys
really drank a lot, huh?
Oh, my God. You should've seen him.
Tearing up the dance floor.
DAPHNE: (CHUCKLES) Really?
Can't drink like that
anymore. I'm out of practice.
HARPER: Hmm.
DAPHNE: Well, I did some damage myself,
and I have the receipts to prove it.
So Christmas is going
to be molto Italiano.
- CAMERON: Oh, kill me now.
- (CHUCKLES)
- (SMOOCHES)
- (CAMERON SIGHS DEEPLY)
- Are you okay?
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
(WAVES CRASHING)
- (MUSIC FADING)
- (SIGHS)
(IN ITALIAN)
Sì.
(SIGHS)
(FRENETIC MUSIC PLAYING)
Yeah!
No, Mia. No!
Vado.
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
("UN ANNO D'AMORE" BY MINA PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(IN ENGLISH) So, you see?
It's just been a series of...
(BREATHES DEEPLY) ...
very bad decisions.
- No. You've had very bad luck.
- I know, I know.
You're like the... the heroine
of your own Italian opera.
Does that mean I'm doomed?
No. Of course, it doesn't.
You're too fabulous to be sad.
Look where you are.
Drink your rosé.
Best thing about luck
is, it can always change.
Do you really believe that?
No.
- (CHUCKLES) Wow.
- (QUENTIN CHUCKLES)
(SONG CONTINUES)
(SONG CONCLUDES)
Your friend didn't come.
Oh, yeah. No, she came, but, uh,
she's over there.
I don't want her to see me pointing.
- (PORTIA CHUCKLES)
- (INDISTINCT CHATTER)
She left you alone. That's not nice.
It's fine, honestly. It's no big deal.
Can I have her chair?
Yeah. Sure, I mean...
- LUCIA: Yeah?
- Might as well.
(INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING)
Hi. I'm Lucia.
- Albie. Hi.
- LUCIA: Hi.
- (LUCIA CHUCKLES)
- Um, so, w... where you from?
Um... I'm from Catania.
- Oh, cool.
- Yeah.
I think... I think we're
going there at some point.
(GIUSEPPE CHUCKLES)
- Ciao.
- GIUSEPPE: Ciao.
(IN ITALIAN)
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
- Hmm?
- (CHUCKLES)
(MUSIC INTENSIFIES)
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
- (BREATHES HEAVILY)
- (GIUSEPPE MUTTERING IN ITALIAN)
(IN ENGLISH) Okay.
- (SPEAKS ITALIAN)
- Sì.
(MUSIC SWELLS, TURNS DRAMATIC)
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(DIDIER GREETING IN FRENCH AND ITALIAN)
Ciao! Ciao!
(IN ENGLISH) So, do you like
this blue Sicilian water?
- (MUSIC TURNS INTRIGUING)
- Yeah. Of course.
It's beautiful.
LUCIA: Yeah, beautiful. I have an idea.
Do you want to go for a swim?
Um...
(INDISTINCT CHATTER AND LAUGHTER)
- Yeah. Yeah, sure.
- Yeah.
- Yeah. Let's go.
- Let's go.
- (CHUCKLING)
- (CHURCH BENCH CREAKING)
(GIUSEPPE AND MIA BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GIUSEPPE MUTTERING IN ITALIAN)
(MOANS)
(PANTS)
(SIGHS)
- (BREATHES HEAVILY)
- (GROANS)
- Whoo! (SPEAKING ITALIAN)
- No, no, no.
- (SIGHS)
- (PANTS)
Yeah.
(SIGHS)
Eh?
(MUSIC TURNS INTRIGUING)
(MUTTERS INDISTINCTLY)
ALBIE: (IN ENGLISH) You
said your name is Lucia?
- LUCIA: "Lucia." Yes.
- ALBIE. Lucia.
- (MUSIC CONTINUES)
- (CONVERSING INDISTINCTLY)
LUCIA: So, you live
in Los Angeles, right?
ALBIE: Yeah.
LUCIA: I always wanted
to go to Los Angeles.
That is my dream!
You've only ever lived in Sicily?
- Yeah.
- ALBIE: Wow!
- Your English is really good.
- Really?
- Yeah. It's amazing.
- LUCIA: Thank you.
ALBIE: Yeah.
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
MIA: (SHOUTING) Luci!
(IN ITALIAN)
(CLICKS TONGUE)
Ciao!
ALBIE: (IN ENGLISH) What she want?
Uh...
She always ask for
something, but I don't care.
ALBIE: How do you say, "I
don't care," in Italian?
LUCIA: Uh, "Non me ne fotte!"
(MUSIC TURNS FRENETIC)
(IN ITALIAN)
- (SIGHS)
- (MIA BREATHES HEAVILY)
- (EXHALES)
- (MUSIC CONCLUDES)
(SIGHS)
Hmm?
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
(SIGHS, BREATHES HEAVILY)
- (CHUCKLES)
- (MUTTERS IN ITALIAN)
(SIGHS)
(DREAMY MUSIC PLAYING)
(IN ENGLISH) Next time, leave
your husband. Come to Èze.
Yeah. We know everybody.
- Really?
- DIDIER: We... We take you everywhere.
You understand little bit French?
TANYA: Oui, un petit peu.
- DIDIER: (IN ENGLISH) Tell us.
- HUGO: Ooh!
Yeah. Look, listen.
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
- DIDIER: (IN ENGLISH) Come on.
- (SPEAKING FRENCH)
- DIDIER: Oh!
- (CHUCKLES)
(ALL LAUGH)
(EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
ETHAN: (IN ENGLISH) Yeah,
'cause, like, Jack Dorsey,
he does barrel saunas.
- CAMERON: Crazy.
- ETHAN: I think he only eats dinner.
- CAMERON: What?
- ETHAN: Or, like, he fasts at the weekends.
I wanna get one of those hyperbaric,
- uh, chambers, you know?
- DAPHNE: Mm.
- CAMERON: Put it in... put it in the house.
- ETHAN: Why?
CAMERON: (SCOFFS) So I
can fucking live forever.
ETHAN: A hundred and eighty years old.
DAPHNE: I don't wanna live forever.
I really don't wanna be old.
- CAMERON: Oh, baby.
- ETHAN: No.
CAMERON: You're... you're
never gonna be old to me.
- No?
- CAMERON: No, never.
What about your workout,
man? You're looking jacked.
ETHAN: Uh, I don't know.
I just, like, go running
and I do some, like,
body weight stuff...
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
(WAVES LAPPING)
(WAVES CRASHING)
(SEAGULLS SQUAWKING)
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
(IN ITALIAN)
(GIUSEPPE GRUNTS)
Uh-huh.
- Hmm? Ah.
- MIA: Your hair.
Ah! Uh...
- (MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
- (BREATHES HEAVILY)
(SEAGULLS SQUAWKING)
ETHAN: (IN ENGLISH) Are you ready?
HARPER: Mm-hmm.
(MUSIC FADES)
Okay. (SIGHS)
What is going on with you?
You've been acting
like a zombie all day.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Is it them? Like, do you not want to go
to dinner with them?
Are you sick of them?
Are you ever going to talk to me again?
What happened yesterday?
We just...
went Jet Skiing, and then...
and then we drank too much.
Who were you with?
Um...
each other, and...
I guess we talked to s...
like, other people at the bar.
What other people?
(SCOFFS) Like, no one I
would ever talk to again.
Just random people.
- Random guys or random girls?
- ETHAN: Random both. Why?
- What? (CHUCKLES)
- (SCOFFS)
- Okay.
- What are...
What are you worried about? Like...
- (KNOCKING ON DOOR)
- (SIGHS)
ETHAN: (SIGHS HEAVILY) Oh, my God.
- (BOTH CHUCKLING)
- ETHAN: (CHUCKLES) Hey.
- Hey!
- Hey! What's up?
- DAPHNE: You guys ready?
- Yes!
- Let's do it. I'm hungry.
- DAPHNE: Me too.
- I like that outfit.
- Thank you!
You know, two months ago,
I couldn't even fit into it.
- Baby weight is such a bitch.
- HARPER: Yeah.
(INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING)
You coming, big guy?
Yeah.
Yeah, I just gotta get
a key. (BREATHES DEEPLY)
- (MUSIC CONCLUDES)
- (CUTLERY CLINKING)
- (SOFT PIANO MUSIC PLAYING)
- I really like those guys.
Don't you?
If you're looking for a friend,
gay guys are really the best.
Because, let's face it,
women are kinda...
depressing.
Oh.
You think?
Yeah. I think most women are drips.
But it's not their fault.
Yeah. They have a lot
to be depressed about.
But you know, they are not fun.
These gay guys are fun.
I think that nephew really likes you.
- No. (CHUCKLES) No.
- TANYA: Yeah. I do.
Do you like him?
- He is pretty hot.
- What's up? Buonasera.
(ALL GREETING IN ITALIAN AND FRENCH)
(IN ENGLISH) You look stunning.
- (INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- (BLOWS KISS)
(BLOWS KISS, CHUCKLES)
- Missed me?
- A little.
(CHUCKLES) Did you miss me?
I put on fresh underwear for ya.
Why? Did you shit your pants? (CHUCKLES)
- No. They're my sexy underwear.
- Oh.
I put 'em on for special
occasions, don't I?
(PORTIA CHUCKLES)
It's all right. I'll
model them for you later.
- We'll see about that.
- (OFF-KEY) ♪ L is for the way you look at me ♪
♪ O is for the only one I see ♪
♪ V is very, very extraordinary ♪
♪ E is even more than
anyone that you adore can ♪
- ♪ And love... ♪
- BERT: Jesus Christ.
- He's worse than usual.
- (CHUCKLES)
- Hey.
Do you guys, um, mind
if I skip dinner tonight?
I... I met someone at the beach,
and I was kind of hoping
to have dinner with her.
"Her"? Yeah.
Sure, go do your thing. We're fine.
Cool. Thanks. Um...
- I'll see you at breakfast.
- DOMINIC: See you then.
- Yep.
- (CHAIR SCRAPING)
- BERT: Good luck!
- ALBIE: Good night.
Good for him.
Jealous?
- Of what?
- (BERT SCOFFS)
- Come on. A little?
- No!
I am. A little.
I may never see a naked woman again.
Although, I did see
one today in my room.
The same girls I saw coming
out of your room yesterday
were in my room today.
I walked in on them, and
one of them was half-naked.
What were they doing in your room?
BERT: (CHUCKLES) I have no idea.
But it was a nice surprise.
(CHUCKLES)
(LAUGHS, SIGHS)
♪ Two in love can make it ♪
♪ Take my heart and
please don't break it ♪
- ♪ Love is made for me and you ♪
- (SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
Actually, I think it's fun. You know?
- (PIANO MUSIC STOPS)
- (INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
- (THUD AGAINST PIANO)
- (SHARP PIANO NOTES ECHO)
- (CROWD GASPS)
- (GASPS) Oh, my God!
MIA: (IN ITALIAN)
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
(IN ENGLISH) Four for dinner.
- (EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
- (GIUSEPPE GROANING)
- (CHUCKLES)
- ISABELLA: Ciao.
Ciao.
- (MUSIC FADES)
- (CHUCKLES)
(IN ITALIAN)
- VALENTINA: Sì.
- (CHUCKLES)
Uh... (CHUCKLES)
ISABELLA: Ah.
Sì.
Prego.
(BREATHES HEAVILY) Uh...
Ah. Sì.
- ISABELLA: (IN ENGLISH) Okay.
- (CHUCKLES) Okay.
- (CHUCKLES)
- VALENTINA: (IN ITALIAN)
VALENTINA: Sì.
(SIRENS BLARING IN DISTANCE)
VALENTINA: (IN ENGLISH) Okay.
(SIRENS DRAW NEARER)
ISABELLA: (IN ITALIAN)
- ROCCO: Valentina!
- Huh?
(LIGHT DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
(IN ENGLISH) Hey. Ciao. (PANTS)
(IN ITALIAN)
(CLICKS TONGUE, SIGHS)
- (GASPS) Mia.
- Lucia.
Allora...
(LUCIA GRUNTS AFFIRMINGLY)
(CHUCKLES)
- (LUCIA SIGHS HEAVILY)
- (IMITATES GASPING)
(IMITATES GASPING)
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
ALBIE: Ciao. (IN ENGLISH) Hi.
Hi. Hey.
Um. So, my dad's cool if
you still wanna have dinner?
Oh, really? Great.
- Um, let's have a drink first.
- Okay, sure. Yeah.
- (MIA CHUCKLING)
- Do you remember my friend, Mia?
ALBIE: Of course, hi. Ciao.
- Piacere. Mia. Ciao.
- ALBIE: Albie.
Um, so... so what are we drinking?
- Gin and tonic?
- Sure. I'll do...
- I'll... Three Gin and tonics?
- Uh, for me, spritz.
- T... Okay. Two gin and tonics and a spritz.
- LUCIA: Yeah.
(INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING)
Hey.
Those are the girls.
The ones in my room.
Now, Albie's with them. (CHUCKLES)
Like father, like father,
like son. (CHUCKLES)
DAPHNE: That was disturbing.
I have this really,
really close girlfriend.
She has a son that has autism,
so we decided to do
a 10K to raise money.
And, um, and I trained a bunch for it.
And I'm going, and there's this guy
that's sort of running next to me.
And all of a sudden, he
just drops to the ground.
Out of nowhere. I mean,
it was, like, surreal.
And he died.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER AND LAUGHTER)
Hey. Uh...
I just want to say thank
you so much for today
because lately I've just
been really low and...
I don't know, I feel like...
- I feel so much better now.
- QUENTIN: Oh, good.
Well, I am a huge
advocate for distraction.
My whole life has been
one long distraction.
- (TANYA CHUCKLES)
- (CHUCKLES)
Well, I just...
I want to thank you for including us
and, um, just...
You know, all of you for
being so friendly, you know.
Why don't you come with
us to Palermo tomorrow.
We're taking Hugo and
Didier on the boat.
We're having a big party at the villa.
- ("TI RUBERÒ" BY BRUNO LAUZI PLAYING)
- You have to see the villa
and the boat.
It's like, a really big party?
- Oh, yes.
- Yes.
- Mm-hmm. (CHUCKLES)
- (CHUCKLES)
- And we'll find you
a terribly well-hung Italian
stud. Heterosexual even.
(CHUCKLES)
(ALL CHUCKLE)
I mean, I'm married, but...
(WHISPERING) We won't tell.
It is tempting.
- Come.
- So, yes?
- Yeah.
- Yes.
- QUENTIN: Oh. Please? Tanya.
- (TANYA CHUCKLES)
(GROUP ENCOURAGING)
I think you're coming.
(CHUCKLES) W... Yes! I will.
(SONG CONTINUES)
Well, no singing around
the piano tonight, girls.
Well, I just hope he's not dead.
Well, maybe they'll find a better one.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER AND CHUCKLING)
Quentin's very nice. I like him a lot.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Where are you going?
PORTIA: I don't know.
No, you're not going to bed.
It's still early. Let's get fucked.
PORTIA: Okay.
- JACK: Yes, geezer.
- PORTIA: Hi!
Uh, two gin and tonics...
- Dos Jägermeister.
- (CHUCKLES)
- Dos Red Bull.
- I'll just have...
(CHUCKLES) I'll just have
one... one gin and tonic.
- What?
- Grazie. For me, just...
Do you know the Italian gestures?
- (MIA SPEAKING ITALIAN)
- (IN ENGLISH) Uh, okay. Uh-huh. Like this?
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
One... One Jägermeister, one Red Bull.
- And this. When you...
- (JACK SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
... when you don't give a fuck.
ALBIE: Yeah, sorry. Yeah.
You don't care about something.
- Like... like this.
- Oh, okay.
- Like, "I don't care."
- Yeah.
- MIA: And... and then...
- Like, I don't care.
(SONG CONTINUES)
- (CARD READER BEEPS)
- (DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
- (CARD READER BEEPS)
- (DOOR OPENS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(SONG CONCLUDES)
I feel like we should, um,
go drink over there, or...
not be here. I don't know. Hm.
What? What's wrong with you, why?
- (LIGHT TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
- I feel bad.
You feel...
He's having a fucking great time.
He's doing all right.
He's just so sweet.
- JACK: Yeah, he's lovely.
- Mm-hmm.
You clearly want to make him jealous,
- so let's make him jealous.
- I... I...
I don't want to make him jealous.
- Yeah, you do.
- No.
- Yeah, you fucking do.
- Oh.
And then I graduated.
I went to Stanford.
- LUCIA: Mm-hmm.
- Yeah. And, um,
I moved back home.
And I was like, "Now what?"
And, um...
- (SMACKS LIPS)
- (MUSIC CONCLUDES)
(CHUCKLES)
Um...
I think, I'm... I think,
I'm going to leave.
- LUCIA: Mm.
- I'm gonna go.
Don't let her win.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
(PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING)
That's a twist.
- JACK: Fucking... Hello!
- Mm-hmm.
(EXHALES) Wow...
(CLICKS TONGUE)
Yeah.
- Um... Mm-mm.
- You all right? You look uncomfortable.
Let's, uh, let's go to my room. Yes.
- (CHUCKLES)
- Fucking... Right!
I think we won.
- (CHUCKLES)
- (GIGGLES)
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
- Here we go. Come here.
- (GROANS SOFTLY)
- (GRUNTS)
- (GROANS)
- Oh, yeah. That's the good stuff.
- Yeah. (INHALES DEEPLY)
(GROANS SOFTLY)
- I, uh, missed you last night.
- (GROANS SOFTLY)
- I missed you too, baby.
- Mm...
Don't you ever leave me again. Okay?
- I won't.
- You promise?
Yeah, I promise.
(CAMERON BREATHES DEEPLY)
(PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(SNIFFLES)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
What happened last night?
Nothing. I told you.
I mean... (INHALES DEEPLY)
... there was one thing that happened.
I guess, you were right.
Cameron asked me to invest
money with him. So...
Probably is the reason
they invited us on vacation.
That's it?
What are you worried about?
Nothing.
(DREAMY MUSIC PLAYING)
PORTIA: (CHUCKLES) Oh!
- (BREATHES DEEPLY) Wow!
- JACK: Sexy, right?
Do you like them?
- Yeah?
- (CHUCKLES) Yes, they're really great.
- PORTIA: Yeah. I think...
- (SPANKS)
- JACK: Ooh, hello.
- (PORTIA CHUCKLING)
- JACK: You're naughty.
PORTIA: Hi. (CHUCKLES)
Hi.
(ALBIE BREATHING HEAVILY)
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
I think I'm gonna cum.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Can I cum? I'm gonna cu...
I'm cumming. (GASPS, MOANS)
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
(GASPS, PANTS)
Oh, my God.
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
(GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING)
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.MY-SUBS.com -